Guide to the North Carolina State University, Libraries, Triangle Research Libraries Network Records
North Carolina State University, Libraries, Triangle Research Libraries Network Records
1979-1997
1979 1997
Triangle Research Libraries Network
UA 012.004
The records of the North Carolina State University Libraries' involvement in the Triangle Research Libraries Network (TRLN) include committee/subcommittee information and meeting minutes, correspondence, memoranda, manuals and information on training procedures, newsletters, and other general information about the committees, subcommittees, activities, and services of TRLN. Materials range in date from 1979 to 1997.
The consortium known today as the Triangle Research Libraries Network (TRLN) started with a collaboration betwen Duke University and the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill in the 1930s to share the development of their respective collections. North Carolina State College began participating in these cooperative collection development programs in the 1950s. In 1977, this group became known as the Triangle University Library Cooperative Committee (TULCC), and adopted the curent name of TRLN in the fall of 1980. North Carolina Central University joined the consortia in 1995, with the current mission of the TRLN continuing to be the joint development of collections and resources as shared between the four member libraries. Representatives from the North Carolina State University libraries (as well as from the three other member libraries) participate in various committees, subcommittees, task forces, and project groups for the joint TRLN efforts.
4.5 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Transferred from North Carolina State University, Libraries.
The records of the North Carolina State University Libraries' involvement in the Triangle Research Libraries Network (TRLN) are arranged alphabetically by topic or committee, and then chronolgically within.
The consortium known today as the Triangle Research Libraries Network (TRLN) started with a collaboration betwen Duke University and the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill in the 1930s to share the development of their respective collections. North Carolina State College began participating in these cooperative collection development programs in the 1950s. In 1977, this group became known as the Triangle University Library Cooperative Committee (TULCC), and adopted the curent name of TRLN in the fall of 1980. North Carolina Central University joined the consortia in 1995, with the current mission of TRLN continuing to be the joint development of collections and resources as shared between the four member libraries. Representatives from North Carolina State University Libraries (as well as from the three other member libraries) participate in various committees, subcommittees, task forces, and project groups for the joint TRLN efforts.
The consortium known today as the Triangle Research Libraries Network (TRLN) started with a collaboration betwen Duke University and the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill in the 1930s to share the development of their respective collections. North Carolina State College began participating in these cooperative collection development programs in the 1950s. In 1977, this group became known as the Triangle University Library Cooperative Committee (TULCC), and adopted the curent name of TRLN in the fall of 1980. North Carolina Central University joined the consortia in 1995, with the current mission of the TRLN continuing to be the joint development of collections and resources as shared between the four member libraries. Representatives from the North Carolina State University libraries (as well as from the three other member libraries) participate in various committees, subcommittees, task forces, and project groups for the joint TRLN efforts.
The records of the North Carolina State University Libraries' involvement in the Triangle Research Libraries Network (TRLN) include committee/subcommittee information and meeting minutes, correspondence, memoranda, manuals and information on training procedures, newsletters, and other general information about the committees, subcommittees, activities, and services of TRLN. Materials range in date from 1979 to 1997.
North Carolina State University Libraries; Triangle Research Libraries Network; Triangle Research Libraries Network; North Carolina State University--History; North Carolina Library cooperation; North Carolina Academic libraries
- Acquisitions/Serials Advisory Committee (1 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Acquisitions/Serials Advisory Committee (2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Acquisitions/Serials Advisory Committee: Report and Recommendations, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Acquisitions/Serials Advisory Committee: Automated Acquisitions/Serials control system functionality requirements, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bibliographic Information System (BIS): Online editing system, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bibliographic Information System: Information Desk, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bibliographic Information System Manual (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bibliographic Information System Manual (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Bibliographic Information System: System Evaluation Subcommittee, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bibliographic Information System: Task Force meeting minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Bibliographic Information System: Training materials, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Bibliographic Information System: Departmental contact information, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Bibliographic Information System: Memoranda, meeting minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Bibliographic Information System: Furniture Subcommittee, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Bibliographic Information System: Training materials, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Bibliographic Information System: Advanced training session, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Bibliographic Information System Manual, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Bibliographic Information System Maual update pages, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Bibliographic Information System: Training, subject heading searches, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Bibliographic Information System: Logo, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Bibliographic Information System: User Training Subcommittee, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Bibliographic Information System Manual, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Bibliographic Information System: Training materials, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Cataloging Policy Committee meeting minutes (1 of 3), 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Cataloging Policy Committee meeting minutes (2 of 3), 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Cataloging Policy Committee meeting minutes (3 of 3), 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Cataloging Transition Subcommittee, 1984-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Circulation Control Subsystem: Memoranda, reports, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Circulation Control Subsystem project, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Coordinating Committee (1 of 3), 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Coordinating Committee (2 of 3), 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Coordinating Committee (3 of 3), 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Coordinating Committee meeting minutes (1 of 5), 1980-1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Coordinating Committee meeting minutes (2 of 5), 1980-1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Coordinating Committee meeting minutes (3 of 5), 1980-1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Coordinating Committee meeting minutes (4 of 5), 1980-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Coordinating Committee meeting minutes (5 of 5), 1980-1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Data Research Associates (DRA) Implementation Group meeting minutes, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Data Research Association (DRA) Issues Group meeting minutes (1 of 3), 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Data Research Association (DRA) Issues Group meeting minutes (2 of 3), 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Data Research Association (DRA) Issues Group meeting minutes (3 of 3), 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Data Research Associates (DRA) newsletter, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Equipment acquisitions, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- General records, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- General records (1 of 2), 1980-1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- General records (2 of 2), 1980-1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- General records (1 of 3), 1980-1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- General records (2 of 3), 1980-1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- General records (3 of 3), 1980-1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Liason and Implementation Committee (1 of 2), 1984-1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Liason and Implementation Committee (2 of 2), 1984-1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes (various committees), 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes (various subcommittees), 1986-1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Monographic Task Force, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Project Status Reports (1 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Project Status Reports (2 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Project Status Reports, 1983-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Reference Manual for Holdings, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Reference Manual for Holdings replacement pages, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Remote Access Subcommittee, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Serial Ordering and Receiving Reorganization Team (SORRT), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Systems Advisory Committee meeting minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Technical Committee (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Technical Committee (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- TRLN Information Update newsletter, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)